Sushma: Good afternoon, everyone. I request, please turn on your videos. Welcome to the Marketing Interviews. I'm Sushma.
Sushma: Hrho Measure Foundation, Roman Egg Foche.
Sushma: So our first, round will be the group discussion.
Sushma: So, in this ju… in this group discussion, we are going to discuss about what do you understand of APOG,
Sushma: And, what do you understand about,
Sushma: marketing intern role at Tamasha Foundation. So, you received the job description, while you're receiving the Google Forms. So, about us, about role, clearly mentioned in the job description.
Sushma: If you would like to take time, 3 minutes, 3 to 4 minutes, please take it and note down the points and share your understanding one after one.
Sushma: Just, it's like a group discussion.
Sushma: I'm like, Leo, to three of you?
Sushma: All right.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Yes.
Sushma: Anyone, please take initiative and start discussing. First of all, let's discuss about, like, what do you understand about FOG?
Sushma: Nice! I'm all open to you.
Swetcha: Yes, Sushma, you are notable.
Sushma: Shyam question what the, is something about Foji?
Sushma: Anyone of you? I'm not calling out the names, anyone have to take the initiative, and…
Sushma: And bhawna, your voice background noise is coming, something, it's growing something.
bhawna tyagi: Let me check… just a second.
Sushma: You can unmute this device from… and you can lock, you know, join from other device, and use that device, voice.
Sushma: With this device, you can disconnect the audio.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Manoj and ROHIT.
ROHIT SHAW: Yes, ma'am?
Sushma: Yeah, what do you understand about AIC?
Sushma: About? Please respond, do you need some time, or, are you…
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Actually, your voice is not, clearly audible to me, so…
Sushma: Am I audible to you now?
Sushma: Yeah, please go ahead. What do you understand about avoiding?
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: What do you understand about?
Sushma: About us, about AFUG.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: That's actually, I go through with the job description now, so…
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: It is, marketing intent role is completely, based on the…
Sushma: Lead generation. The marketing engine role, I'm asking… About us, about the organization.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: A46 collab.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: So, actually, I go to the website, so it is, like, focused on the…
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Climate change and, 1002 plastic means completely based on environment.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: been involvement.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: The involvement without plastic.
Sushma: I don't know where you're reading. I don't…
bhawna tyagi: AFLG is a multi-service company that provides IT solution and HR facilities, maybe.
Sushma: Maybe, what maybe? Have you gone through about us?
bhawna tyagi: Okay, bye.
Sushma: While you're applying to any organization.
Sushma: It's like, you know, just to have a look about that organization.
bhawna tyagi: Actually, ma'am, I have applied for multiple organizations, I don't remember.
Sushma: That's the thing, I just, you know, given you 5 minutes of time.
Sushma: To refer that. Who will do during the interview, like, you know, prepare, tell, prepare about us, and tell after 5 minutes.
Sushma: We are given such kind of flexibility.
bhawna tyagi: As per I remember, it is IT Solution and HR facilities that provides clients.
Sushma: Solutions and hip tapping.
Sushma: I'm so sorry. Please take, you know, 5 more minutes. This is the last, like, you know.
Sushma: gray spirit that I would like to give to three of you.
Sushma: Please, first of all, refer what FOG does.
Sushma: We clearly mentioned in the job description, and you can also check the
Sushma: chat, which you receive the Google form. In that, you may receive the job post link. If you click on that, you can see
Sushma: Complete job description.
Sushma: In that, you know about at least airport.
bhawna tyagi: So…
Sushma: Take 5 more minutes, and please do it quickly.
Sushma: Okay, please go ahead.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Yes. That's awful.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: A4D stands for the AI for Good Impact Collaborative.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: It is an, initiative by the, OMSA Foundation.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: That promotes the responsible use of artificial intelligence to solo social challenges.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: The organization focuses on AI governance.
Sushma: Please don't, please don't read, simply, just share what you understand, that's it.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Like, it is, it is completely, like, based on the…
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: To solve the problems, like, the organization mainly focuses on, A, governance, sustainability, and, mental well-being.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Like, it collaborates with the researchers, Policymakers, universities, industries, and professionals.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: to build, ethical AI solutions that benefit, society.
Sushma: Are those…
Sushma: Others, no understanding?
ROHIT SHAW: I mean, like you said, A4G has, the three core pillars, which are governance of AI, AI for mental well-being, and
ROHIT SHAW: AI for Sustainability.
ROHIT SHAW: So, basically, AI for governance is using data-driven tools and ethical frameworks for
ROHIT SHAW: like, for, adjusting to the rapid tech shifts, and AI for material, sorry, mental well-being is using.
ROHIT SHAW: AI models and machine learning for…
ROHIT SHAW: Training them so that they can understand human mental well-being.
ROHIT SHAW: And AI for sustainability is using, same, like, machine learning models and data analytics to go through all the environmental, social, social goals of an economy.
Sushma: bhawna?
bhawna tyagi: respond.
Sushma: Totally understand. Now, did you at least… after referring, did you change your opinion, starting? You said that it's HR consultant firm?
bhawna tyagi: Yes, ma'am.
Sushma: Now, what do you understand?
bhawna tyagi: As Torres say, there are 3…
bhawna tyagi: Core ideas in which we are focusing.
bhawna tyagi: A4G is for AI for Good, and they are collecting, like, Datas, and through the… which… Deegan?
bhawna tyagi: Use data for the further information and.
Sushma: No, we are not collecting any data, actually. Remove that point. Okay, a part of that, what do you understand?
Sushma: What do you understand about the vision and mission?
Sushma: I don't want to waste the time. Next, what do you understand about the role?
Sushma: It is, do you have any understanding about the role, about the marketing internal role?
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Yes, sir.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: I have, like, one year of experience in this role.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: In my previous organization.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: So, actually, there, I'm asking.
Sushma: experience. I will ask your experience. Now, I just want to hear what do you understand
Sushma: About the role, which is mentioned in the job description, marketing internal role.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Yeah.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Basically, this role is completely… you have to generate the leads using different types of,
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: It looks like, in using Job Poster, or LinkedIn, Facebook, Instagram.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: We have to generate the leads, actually, who have, interested in it, so we have to find the potential customers.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Based on that, we have to… Work on it, like, After generating the target audience.
Sushma: Okay, it's not only the regeneration, it's a mix of… Another thing on top.
Sushma: kaushik?
Sushma: Can you please turn on your video, kaushik?
Sushma: Firstly, why did you join David?
kaushik ranjan: clean.
Sushma: Did you inform to anyone?
kaushik ranjan: I'm actually, I got late due to some reasons.
Sushma: Is it any emergency, family emergency, or medical emergency? I just want to know, so accordingly, I will involve… I will allow you.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, I was just engaged in some paperworks in my college, that's why I got laid.
Sushma: What's your college timings?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, my college time is from 9 to 12, but today there was some paperwork, so that's why it got late.
kaushik ranjan: Okay.
Sushma: Get your objective resume in this Zoom chat box?
Sushma: Quickly.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Others, what do you understand about the role?
Sushma: And by the way, Manoj, you're working as a full-time currently, right?
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Yes, it's actually a worker for the full-time employer, but okay, what's your…
Sushma: What's your office timings?
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: No, currently, I am not working.
Sushma: But you just mentioned a resume present.
Sushma: You didn't put any end date for your experience?
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: 20 days, back, 20 days ago, I resented.
Sushma: Okay, what's the reason that you resigned there?
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Actually, initially they said that, there will be salary hikes, after one month. Okay.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: It's about, like, 10 days.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: 10 months, completed, still, the manager and the HR is not able, like, ready to…
Sushma: Okay, I will discuss those things later, but last, my last question to you is, why not…
Sushma: Another full-time role, why internship opportunity?
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Like, full-time role means, like, it is completely, you have to ready to do any type of work, like.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: In that role, they will not provide any trainings, because I have some amount of experience there. If I apply for any job.
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: So, they will directly, like, to, do the task. They will… don't give any training like that also. And there will be no things to learn in the full-time role. So, while in the internship, we can, have… we have… we can grab some amount of,
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: a knowledge in here, so we can, learn something. So, that's why I chose this role as an intern, because.
Sushma: Learn, in your full time. Now, why again in intern?
MONOJ KUMAR MALI: Yes, I said no. In 10, we have to learn so many of things we can learn here, but in full-time role, there will be no chance of it.
Sushma: So, kaushik, what do you understand about, organization, about us, A4G?
Sushma: Unmute yourself.
kaushik ranjan: At the very first I understand about this organization is that this organization is working on the sustainability and the ethical use of AI in sustainable development.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: That's it?
kaushik ranjan: Thank God.
Sushma: What do you understand about the role?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, currently I have to work, from, I think 5 in the evening to 8.
kaushik ranjan: So…
Sushma: by the way.
Sushma: asking the work timings, I just want to hear the roles and responsibilities that you understand from the job description.
kaushik ranjan: Let's too late.
Sushma: 2 to 3 minutes time, and refer it and let me know what do you understand. Rest of people, please, ROHIT and, Pavna, you didn't share about your role, understand?
bhawna tyagi: Lead generation and data analytics.
Sushma: No, it's not Data Nan.
Sushma: Tell me, what do you understand the lead generation part?
bhawna tyagi: determination, like… Campaigner role.
Sushma: Hmm.
bhawna tyagi: And understanding the behavior of the audience, and…
bhawna tyagi: Identifying the interest of the audience to generate the leads.
Sushma: We are… no need of understanding the interest, actually.
Sushma: We need to… Generate the interested links.
bhawna tyagi: Okay.
bhawna tyagi: Ma'am, data analytics part, having the analyzing campaign…
Sushma: Analytics means, analytics, it's like, the campaign analytics.
bhawna tyagi: Okay.
bhawna tyagi: Okay, okay.
bhawna tyagi: Means what type of things gonna work, or what type of things don't work for us.
Sushma: Where are you from, bhna?
bhawna tyagi: I'm from Delhi.
Sushma: Alright.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Four of you, I just want to ask that anyone of you aware about the meta ads?
Sushma: Metahead campaigns.
bhawna tyagi: Yes.
Sushma: You were aware of it, right?
Sushma: What do you know? Like, can you please quickly tell me, do you have hands-on experience in meta-ad campaigns?
bhawna tyagi: Actually, no, but I understand it. Actually, I don't work on it practically.
Sushma: Okay.
bhawna tyagi: But what is…
Sushma: You just know about the theoretical understanding, not a practical exposure, right?
bhawna tyagi: Yeah.
Sushma: Tell me what your theoretical understanding.
bhawna tyagi: We have to connect, first of all, our Facebook and Instagram page to the Meta Business Show, through which we can run ad campaigns for.
Sushma: Okay, okay, okay, I just want to, like, instead of that, I'm so sorry for interrupting in between. See, for instance, in this organization.
Sushma: We do have essay contest conta- essay contest.
Sushma: And our target audience were senior UZ and PG students, which in humanities, Vision, Humanities, Economics, Public Policy?
Sushma: law, philosophy from these backgrounds, okay? Senior UG and PG students, like, final year UG and final year PG students.
Sushma: That is our first target audience. Second target audience are PhD students and doctoral scholars.
Sushma: Okay? So, the Instagram, Facebook are targeted for these two target audiences.
bhawna tyagi: Yeah.
Sushma: So, what kind of campaign that will you run?
Sushma: To generate interested links.
bhawna tyagi: First of all, we have to understand our audience, their age.
bhawna tyagi: Like, if we are talking about 18 to 25 mostly.
Sushma: 25 we can construct, yeah. Per senior UGNT students.
bhawna tyagi: Yeah.
bhawna tyagi: For these age groups, we can use Instagram and Facebook. They mostly
bhawna tyagi: Have spent their time on these kind of platforms.
bhawna tyagi: So…
Sushma: Yes?
bhawna tyagi: We have to… first of all, we have to see the age group, and second of all, we have to
bhawna tyagi: Know their interest, kind of interest, what kind of…
bhawna tyagi: Like what we can say?
bhawna tyagi: What kind of reels, or maybe anything they want to watch, or…
bhawna tyagi: What kind of interest they have showing?
bhawna tyagi: How do you know.
Sushma: for that interest.
bhawna tyagi: According to the reasons, there are different interests in everything, like, language also are… Different kind of thing.
Sushma: Next, what will you do?
bhawna tyagi: We can run campaign according to the reasons.
bhawna tyagi: Like, we can run a campaign in Denver.
Sushma: I just want to know what kind of campaign that will you run to generate interested leads for this essay contest, focusing senior UC and PC students?
Sushma: At least, can you please tell how many kinds of campaigns that, you know, MetaAt is, you know, Providing…
Sushma: You're not much aware in the kinds of, meta- what kind of, like, you know, based on the objective, we have to choose the
Sushma: type of the campaign, right? Here, I'm telling the objective is generating the interested leads in those target audience.
Sushma: So, you know the object, so what kind of campaign will you…
Sushma: Choose to run on my tag.
bhawna tyagi: Lead generation. For lead generation.
Sushma: In lead generation, under which category of campaign that will you run?
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Oh…
Sushma: Yes, ROHIT, what do you understand about the road?
ROHIT SHAW: Ma'am, I think the role focuses on, building a, Mike, building a…
ROHIT SHAW: Voice of the organization across platforms, like.
ROHIT SHAW: It's basically an integrated marketing system, I think, where you build a voice across platforms, be it LinkedIn, Facebook, Instagram.
ROHIT SHAW: can you hear me?
Sushma: Yeah, yeah, go ahead. Are you… yeah, tell me.
ROHIT SHAW: Yeah, and and… branding…
ROHIT SHAW: And, running campaigns based on the interests as seen, and then converting them to future customers.
ROHIT SHAW: like, the…
Sushma: Sheikh, what do you understand?
kaushik ranjan: memorable.
Sushma: About the role.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, I'm from media, field, so, I've understood that here we have to, design media kits, press releases, and,
kaushik ranjan: Platform-driven strategy, like, the strategy for different platforms will be different for Instagram, the strategy will be different for LinkedIn, the strategy will be more professional than the Instagram handles.
kaushik ranjan: And we have to also generate, data-driven, data-driven outcomes.
Sushma: Don't say that what is, on your screen, just, you know, share what you understand.
Sushma: And the question at which I'm… I'm asking…
Sushma: It's a basic thing, because you apply
Sushma: for this role, I'm asking, what do you understand about us, about their role? If you didn't understand these two things, it's very difficult for you to intern with us.
Sushma: Right? If you didn't understand the basic roles and responsibilities which was mentioned in the job description, how are you going to do your 6 months of internship with us?
kaushik ranjan: Actually, we have to design the brand image through our overall platforms for Instagram, Facebook, LinkedIn, and we have to also design the,
kaushik ranjan: We have also to design the narrative of the, Bonsai Foundation.
Sushma: Alright, and your… so far, whatever you briefed, that is… comes under branding, right? So, branding comes first. After that, what do you understand?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, we have to build a strategy for the program.
Sushma: So along with that lead generation part also comes, okay?
Sushma: And sometimes it's also required to act as a PR.
Sushma: Which, you know, relevant to your study, which is…
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, in PR, we have to deal about the positive aspect also, and in the crisis management role also. Whenever the company needed to maintain its image, then we had to do the crisis management.
Sushma: asking about the payer. I know that you know very good about peer, because as you're studying mass communication, I know that. But now, my question is, what do you know about lead generation?
kaushik ranjan: Actually, I'm more comfortable in working in the media aspect of the field.
Sushma: Yeah, I know that. See, the lead generation comes the social media marketing also.
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am.
kaushik ranjan: And the lead generation, it can be maybe directly, or through…
kaushik ranjan: The lead can be generated directly, or through some, some…
kaushik ranjan: Slow medium also, where the potential users and potential interested users will join us through some data, through links.
kaushik ranjan: and all.
kaushik ranjan: And through their interest, also.
Sushma: See, in the PR, do you think that, lead generation also comes in, though?
Sushma: like, like, PR means here, like, you know, we have to… you have to, first of all.
Sushma: target date…
kaushik ranjan: Massive…
Sushma: Yes. So, you are from mass communication and journalism, right?
Sushma: So…
Sushma: In the PR, our PR also, sometimes… currently, we are not much focusing, to be honest, for the PR. We will be… we will do that.
Sushma: But our main focus in Puya, which is something, you have to, first of all, Shortlist the journalists.
kaushik ranjan: This one.
Sushma: Whom to approach. Outreach them.
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am.
Sushma: Is that interesting?
Sushma: for them.
Sushma: So that they will publish all our events.
Sushma: This is something of PR.
Sushma: Okay, coming to the lead generation.
Sushma: What are the events we are having? We do have a target audience for the participants.
Sushma: like, currently we are not focusing the sponsors and partners, but for current situation for SJ Contest, we do have 4 sets of target audience.
Sushma: segments.
Sushma: You need to, first of all, already the platforms, we decided which platforms that we are targeting them.
Sushma: you need to, first of all, generate the leads. Like, there are two types of… we are focusing, which is social media marketing. Through social media marketing, generating leads, which is, you know, through meta ads, ad promotions.
Sushma: Campus, different types of
Sushma: campaign in meta ad, like that. So, what are the interested leads that you're coming, from that campaigns and from the social media marketing?
Sushma: You need two?
Sushma: hand over those interested leads to growth thing. They will convert into successful registration. So, as a marketing, you… you have to market them. They will look after the sales part.
Sushma: In this social media marketing, you need to be good in video making, poster making, Content, all those things.
Sushma: So, in your resume, I've seen that you're good in videographing, photographing, and editing part as well. I just want to know about those skills.
Sushma: Are you comfortable in creating the reels, and creating the posters, and creating the content for social media marketing?
kaushik ranjan: I am good at Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, and other, Adopt Premiere Pro, all the media-related softwares. I am very comfortable at that. I am currently working
kaushik ranjan: At that, software.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Are you interested to… Learn about MetaX by your bone.
Sushma: My dad campaigns.
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am, I am very interested.
Sushma: Why you're so interested?
Sushma: Actually, I will… What's the reason?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, in the month of June, I was working with Adit Birdla Group as… in their public relations and corporate social responsibility of the grass team.
kaushik ranjan: of the Grasim units. So, there, I was working in the PR field, so they were running some, ads, and in their CSR platform, they were running, initiative, Didi Kidukhan.
kaushik ranjan: in which I have visited all… they have run approximately 20 DDukan, in which they had, seed-funded 20…
kaushik ranjan: 20 tribal women's to run their own initiatives. So, there they were running some, ads on, Instagram and Facebook.
kaushik ranjan: But I didn't… didn't understand the whole concept in one month, so I will be very interested in learning that.
Sushma: All day.
Sushma: Oh… Oh, okay.
Sushma: So…
Sushma: Anything that you would like to add, your understanding about the lead generation? So, now, did you understand about the… what is lead generation and branding part, whatever you said? See, guys, let me brief about, very quickly.
Sushma: This marketing is here. You need to be played as a branding, lead generation, and payer.
Sushma: 3 willcums.
Sushma: But currently, PR is not active. It will come.
Sushma: In future.
Sushma: So, the current is branding. As a branding, you need to create a visibility and credibility towards a target audience.
Sushma: And what kind of statues of visibility and credibility that you have to commit up, and, you know.
Sushma: This visibility and credibility helps the…
Sushma: audience that, you know, keep them… like, we, we, we have to keep the promise trust.
Sushma: In social media
Sushma: And lead generation, whatever is planned. So we… so there are two types of lead generation we are focusing currently, which is email marketing.
Sushma: and social media marketing. Through that, we had to generate the potential leads, which is interested leads.
Sushma: For our full target audience.
Sushma: This is a current, current role will be there, and after that, the future events, the lead generation pack will be focusing not only the participants, but partners and sponsors as well.
Sushma: Cleo?
Sushma: And about the F4G?
Sushma: So, Omisha Foundation having the two initiatives, which is Wong and FOG, Wong means Voice of New Generation, which we provide the 12 to 18 group of school-going students, provide them a platform to raise their voices.
Sushma: So they can, you know, suggest a few innovative ideas towards the sustainability challenges, and we encourage and motivate them to put them into actions.
Sushma: In their locality. And A4G is having the three focus areas, which is A for mental well-being, governance of AI, and A for socioeconomic sustainability.
Sushma: So, we… our vision and mission is something, we believe that, AI should be a natural extension
Sushma: For the human goodness.
Sushma: That is our vision.
Sushma: And, which we… we believe that it shouldn't replace the human values.
Sushma: and mission is something that, we… the name itself suggests that A4G Impact Collaborative, which is, like, you know, AI… AI for Good Impact Collaborative. We…
Sushma: We are looking to collaborate for good impact towards the air for good, and we would like to collaborate, with, policy makers, researchers, global leaders.
Sushma: Like, event sponsors, donors, institutions.
Sushma: Who works towards this? A for good, in these three focus areas.
Sushma: Mostly, like… Oh…
Sushma: we use… we increase fairness and ethical use and good well-being, which, you know, you just covered in a single line. This is a, you know, a very, one word of summary I just want to put on that.
Sushma: And just give us, 2-3 minutes time. We will let you know who we would like to proceed next.
Sushma: Swetcha just joined Rooma.
Sushma: Alright.
Sushma: I was… Guys,
Sushma: ROHIT and Manoj, we appreciate your time and interest, but we are not moving forward with the next round. You both of you can leave the mate.
Sushma: All the best for our future.
Sushma: Okay, so both of you, could you please turn on your videos quickly?
Sushma: Okay. I will ask now.
Sushma: Next questions. I want to hear the answers, one after one. First of all, please share what's your career goal?
Sushma: YA4G?
Sushma: What motivates you to do this internship?
Sushma: And why marketing?
Sushma: Four questions. Let me repeat that. What's your career goal?
Sushma: Why A4GN marketing?
Sushma: Interm?
Sushma: And, what motivates you to do this internship?
kaushik ranjan: non-stable,
Sushma: Go ahead.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, at the very first, as I am currently enrolled in PG program, so, before completing this, my master's degree, I will be gaining some hand-on experience and hand-on, additive
kaushik ranjan: Additive some experience and knowledges, which will help me in further, career goals.
kaushik ranjan: So, I have joined, I have soared my interest to join this internship program, to gain some hand-on experience.
kaushik ranjan: From the Omisha Foundation, and, the very first thing I have,
kaushik ranjan: understand about this foundation is that this foundation is working on sustainability and sustainable development goals 1, 2, 3, and,
kaushik ranjan: I think 10 also, SDG10. So, it will be very, beneficial for me to learn about, this marketing field as
kaushik ranjan: As mass communication not always covers the journalism aspect, it also covers the marketing field, social media, social media handling also.
kaushik ranjan: So, I will be very grateful if I will be learning from your side, which will help me in the near future.
Sushma: Did you cover all the questions?
kaushik ranjan: Patio…
Sushma: What's your career goal?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, through this internship.
Sushma: What's your carrier goal? Career goal?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, I am preparing for, NetJRF, so, I will be moving to that only.
kaushik ranjan: This will…
Sushma: You're cheap.
Sushma: Okay, so when you will be… so, like, is it your final year of PG?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am, it is my final Europe PG.
Sushma: Next, what's your plan?
kaushik ranjan: I am preparing for UGCNet. Previously, I got, I got rejected by 3 to 4 marks, so, this time.
kaushik ranjan: I've also applied, but exam was not good due to short… I was not prepared at all, but in the next attempt, I will be moving to UGCNet.
Sushma: When is your next exam?
kaushik ranjan: I will appear in, May.
kaushik ranjan: It is, next May. Actually, EGNET is covered two times a year, but I'm not prepared for the December one, so I will be giving my reattempt in next May.
Sushma: Okay, when you will be completing your college?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, next May, 2027, ma'am.
kaushik ranjan: May 2, 2027.
Sushma: Okay, alright, alright.
Sushma: And your college timing is up to 12pm, and sometimes you will be back at least by 2 or 3, right?
kaushik ranjan: No, ma'am, sometimes by 1, I will be back.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Do you have any other commitments which is,
Sushma: Online or offline courses, or freelancing things.
kaushik ranjan: Mormon.
kaushik ranjan: Currently.
Sushma: eligible part-time.
kaushik ranjan: No, I'm… currently, I'm not doing any other rules.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: So, you covered your career goal, why you put your… and why marketing, actually? Why marketing intern? You didn't cover that.
kaushik ranjan: I have actually covered. Ma'am, as a media professional, sometimes marketing is also needed at many platforms.
kaushik ranjan: when I… when I was at Adit Birla Group, I have learned about… I have learned something about marketing, as when I was working with Didi Kidugant, it was…
kaushik ranjan: totally, marketing, field of, Adity Berla Group. Through CSR, initiative, they, they were developing marketing roles, to the tribal women's… they were engaging tribal women's, to develop, field aspects, and,
kaushik ranjan: Hello?
Sushma: Hmm, go ahead.
kaushik ranjan: They were actually, developing, the, Didi Kidukhan initiative as a marketing
kaushik ranjan: In the, in the marketing field, they were developing DD Kidu Khan, so I was very,
kaushik ranjan: interested in learning those aspects, as I have no deep knowledge in the field of marketing.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Hmm… All day.
Sushma: Thank you. Bhawana, please, can you please share that, all the questions quickly?
Sushma: All the answers to that question is complete.
bhawna tyagi: Okay.
bhawna tyagi: So, I want to work with the A4G, because they give me exposure to all the aspects as I am a social media… for the social media marketing and role, because I'm enrolling in,
bhawna tyagi: Digital Marketing and Data Analytics course. I'm doing BSc in this period, actually.
bhawna tyagi: And for now, my career goal is to do an internship and work… to have work with some
bhawna tyagi: Good company to handle an experience and all these things to expose her with the field.
bhawna tyagi: And… why is marketing? Because this is my…
bhawna tyagi: mainly filled in my course, so I want to do… this internship.
Sushma: What's your college timings?
bhawna tyagi: My college timings is from 9 to 4.
Sushma: At what time you'll be back from college to whom?
bhawna tyagi: It'll take 20-25 minutes.
Sushma: How your, like,
Sushma: So these internship timings, so from 5pm to 9pm, from between 5pm to 9pm, your presence is very required for team meetings, and one-to-one meetings, everything for planned and unplanned, meetings.
Sushma: And if the meetings are not scheduled in that time slot, you can do your work.
Sushma: And the rest of work you can do in your flexible timings.
Sushma: But the 5 to 9 p.m.
Sushma: Your presence is very required whenever the work and meetings were scheduled.
bhawna tyagi: Okay, come in.
bhawna tyagi: I'll manage it.
Sushma: How you will manage it?
bhawna tyagi: Ma'am, because I'm doing an internship for 6 months, I'll…
bhawna tyagi: you will provide me certificate after completion of that. So, I'll submit it, so they give me some credit of that.
bhawna tyagi: So it will help me out if I'm not taking classes for when to do our last.
Sushma: Oh…
Sushma: So, both of, like, kaushik, are you, comfortable of, committing 6 months? Do you have any other next 6 months, any priorities, and comfortable of committing 5pm to 9pm?
kaushik ranjan: I will be continuing 6 months.
Sushma: Your voice is not clear.
kaushik ranjan: I will be continuing till 6 months.
bhawna tyagi: Okay.
Sushma: Alright.
Sushma: It's a 5 hours of internship program. Are you comfortable to come with 5 hours in a day, which is 30 hours per week?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am.
bhawna tyagi: Switch up… okay. Switch up…
Sushma: Let's, you know, join in the breakout room. Guys, please, you know, hold on for 2-3 minutes, we will be back with the results.
Sushma: Kenny, I'm going to reach out from your end.
Swetcha: Or didn't.
Sushma: So, bhawana, we appreciate your time and interest, but we are not moving forward with the next round. All the best for the future. Have a nice day.
bhawna tyagi: Thank you.
Sushma: Thank you.
Sushma: So, kaushik, where are you from?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, I am from Ghaiji, Bihar.
Sushma: Bihar!
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am, kaushik behalf.
Sushma: Okay, okay.
Sushma: Oh… What do your father, mother do, and siblings?
kaushik ranjan: My father in… my father is in police department, and my mother is of my… my mother is housewife.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: siblings?
kaushik ranjan: Ayum?
kaushik ranjan: Hello?
Sushma: Yeah, yeah, I'm asking about the siblings. You're only a single child, or do you have siblings?
kaushik ranjan: M-O… Hello?
kaushik ranjan: Am I audible?
Sushma: You are audible only, Swetcha is a problem from my end?
Swetcha: Mmm.
Swetcha: I can handle both of you, that's fine.
kaushik ranjan: My father is in Polish department, my mother is housewife, and my sister is preparing for government exams.
Sushma: Alright, elder sister, or anger sister?
kaushik ranjan: elusive.
Sushma: Nope.
Sushma: Elder sister. Elder sister. Okay, okay, okay.
Sushma: Tell me how your career aspiration will be aligned to this internship.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, till now I have understood about this internship is that internship role includes marketing roles. So, through, through my, degree, it will be very helpful in adding some, experience and knowledges from the marketing field.
kaushik ranjan: Which will, help me to gain some extra knowledge and, extra experience, which will be helpful, if, as experience to me after completion… after completion of my degree.
Sushma: Why do you want a marketing exposure in your degree? What will… these marketing… how these marketing exposures will be added
Sushma: In your career.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, as, after, net, we can also move to MNCs, to work.
kaushik ranjan: So, if we have prior knowledge of marketing or some field experience, we will be getting some extra benefits and extra,
kaushik ranjan: Exposure from the industry.
Sushma: What is extra? I didn't get you. What extra?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, skills, when I will be working 6 months with you, so I will be gaining some hand-on skills.
kaushik ranjan: Add-on experience, which will be additive, for me to add… which will help as add-ons, to my previous knowledge.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: What's your last drawn stipend?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am?
Sushma: What's your last, bronze stipend from your previous internship?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, they were, providing $10,000 in, hand, and providing accommodation and other expenses, like fooding, lodging, traveling.
Sushma: Okay, along with the 10K, they're just providing you a combination and food.
Sushma: traveling…
kaushik ranjan: I'm actually using…
Sushma: Okay.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, it, we have free… we'll… I was free for only one month, as college was…
kaushik ranjan: college had given me, one month duration to complete my internship as a… as a credit point in NEP policy. So, we were allowed to do internship for one month only.
kaushik ranjan: So, during…
Sushma: So, Adity, you're telling about that you worked at Aditya Bhila, you just got 10K, the recent one, and along with the combination food and travel as well. Is it on-site internship?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am? Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am, it was on-site.
Sushma: As a PR and CSR department, okay. It's one month only, you just, work there.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: And here I can see that some other NGVo company just, you know, worked as a social media handler.
Sushma: Yes, ma'am. Are you currently working there?
kaushik ranjan: No, ma'am, no. I had exited from there.
Sushma: When, when, when did you ex… exhibits.
kaushik ranjan: I exit in April, ma'am.
Sushma: April 2026?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am.
Sushma: It seems like you work to one of them.
Sushma: Two years almost there, right?
kaushik ranjan: Actually, it… it is my brother's and you.
Sushma: Great.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: So you've just given us support there, is it cousin… cousin?
kaushik ranjan: There's some cousin brother.
Sushma: Okay.
kaushik ranjan: He was studying with me in sociology department, so, we, along with our cousins, we started an NGO based in Gaya.
kaushik ranjan: So, previous year, we got a CSR from, Amazon Foundation through DonateCard.
Sushma: Great! Where did you get that, like, you know, CSF earning from that MSN?
kaushik ranjan: through DonateCart. DonateCart is a, an institution which provides CSR off Amazon.
kaushik ranjan: So, through the credit card, it, we have got the CSR, to our, NGO.
Sushma: Now, are you not working… are you not a part in that NGO?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, officially, I am not part of that NGO currently.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Alright,
Sushma: See here, whatever you managed in that NGO, are you comfortable… if you got shortlisted, are you comfortable of managing whole social media accounts?
Sushma: and content also in that social media. Are you comfortable to do this kind of work?
Sushma: It's a part of marketing.
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am, I can do it.
Sushma: Do you have any offers or interviews in pipeline?
kaushik ranjan: this, ma'am?
kaushik ranjan: Do you have offers?
Sushma: offers or interviews in pipeline? Any, you know, lined up any interviews or offers in pipeline, something, you know, in hand?
kaushik ranjan: Mom.
Sushma: No?
Sushma: Are you not currently act… are you not actively… Applying… applying the internships?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, I was… I had applied for 2 to 3 internships, but it was on… it was the pro… the internship required on-site requirement.
kaushik ranjan: But I… I can't, go to do internship on…
kaushik ranjan: on-site, so I had applied for remote internship.
Sushma: Oakland.
Sushma: So, have you referred our stipends, Rachel?
Sushma: That which we mentioned in the job description.
kaushik ranjan: Excellent.
Sushma: What do you understand from that?
kaushik ranjan: About the stipend structure.
Sushma: Yeah.
kaushik ranjan: For the first 2 months, actually, it was 5, I think, and…
kaushik ranjan: then 7.5, then for the last 2 months, I think it was 10.
Sushma: Let me add on that, these are the benchmark amounts for every 2 months.
Sushma: If you inverse 30 hours per week of every month.
Sushma: Then only you will receive these benchmarks.
Sushma: Yes, ma'am. For first 2 months, if you invest 30 hours per week.
Sushma: You will receive 5K per month for first 2 months. After that, the first 2 months' performance will be evaluated and repressed for third and fourth month.
Sushma: If you're rating above 4,
Sushma: And again, if you invest 30 hours per week, then only the third and fourth month, you will get $7,500 as a benchmark of full limit.
Sushma: If you didn't invest 30 hours per week, instead of 30 hours, you just invested 20 hours, or 15 hours, or 25 hours, you will get the stipend for those 20 or 15, or
Sushma: Amount that you invested for that week.
Sushma: Okay
Sushma: Same applies. Your 3rd and 4th month performance will be evaluated and appraised for 5th and 6th month. Again, if your rating is out of 5 above 4,
Sushma: Then you will be…
Sushma: you know, rated, like, if you… if you're in the study of COVID, then you can see that, benchmark amount for 10K for 5th and 6th month.
Sushma: Do you have any concerns or queries in this type instructor?
kaushik ranjan: Maura.
Sushma: Are you comfortable with this?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am.
Sushma: Why you're comfortable with this? Because last month, you just run 10K with all facilities, so…
Sushma: Alliances, and now,
Sushma: You're just, you know, it's a remote internship, and it's your pace, you're starting two months' pay, next two months is not, you know, matching to your recent one.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, the only benefit for me through this internship is that it is actually a remote internship, and I can attend my college also, and do the remote at the same time.
kaushik ranjan: So, actually, I don't have, gaps between my degrees, so it will be very hard for me to go to work on-site
kaushik ranjan: Currently. So, through this remote work, it will be beneficial for me, to continue my college and the remote internship also.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Do you have any questions to ask us?
kaushik ranjan: Till now… Ma'am, how the rating points, you have mentioned about 5-point ratings.
Sushma: Very good question. Okay. See, there are two parameters to evaluate the performance. The first one is KRS of your role, key result areas.
Sushma: Individual goals which is given to you.
Sushma: In a month. A milestone set by the PM.
Sushma: So, based on this, your performance rating will be… Given?
Sushma: And the second parameter is values. We do have five core values at Omisha Foundation, which is
Sushma: Integrity and authenticity, ownership and alignment, agility.
Sushma: innovation and imagination, prosper, and acceptance. So, towards these three, these, towards these, five core values, if you're showing good, like, you know, values in each value,
Sushma: in… throughout your 6 months, like, in day-to-day operations, so that, you know, it will be evaluated. So, average of values and average of,
Sushma: Your performance will be rated out of 5.
Sushma: Clean?
Sushma: Can you…
kaushik ranjan: Okay, clear, ma'am.
Sushma: Okay, so, let me give it to Swetcha. Swetcha can take the… both an HR treatment for branding and lead generation, one after one. Over to you.
Swetcha: Okay, Sushma, thank you. So, hi, kaushik, my name is Swetcha, and I am the HRBP for Marketing at A4G.
Swetcha: So tell me, how would you promote something you don't believe in?
kaushik ranjan: How will you promote in…
Swetcha: Like, for instance, there is something that doesn't align with your values, and we are asking you to promote that. How would you promote that to your audience?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, it is…
kaushik ranjan: It is my role to work with you. So, aligning my values and ideology, is not a core area to align with the field. So, whatever the work allows me to do, whatever the work allows me to work with
kaushik ranjan: good ethics, I can work with that.
kaushik ranjan: Aligning ideas is not part of the work culture.
kaushik ranjan: Like…
Swetcha: What if it is against your ethics?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am?
Swetcha: What if the thing we are asking you to promote is against your ethics?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, I was not talking about my ethics. I was talking about the work ethics. If the work ethics, allows it to do it, I will be working, with it.
Swetcha: All right. Share an example where communication failed, and why did it fail?
kaushik ranjan: Share an example.
Swetcha: Where communication failed, and why did it fail?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, communication, can fail, due to various reasons. If we are talking about something, we are using,
kaushik ranjan: sentences and, verbs, like, which, which can't be understood by the, your potential, consumers and all. So, their communication, can gap, communication gap can gap due to technical errors, due to, translation errors, due to cultural errors also.
kaushik ranjan: If we are not aligning our communication goals with the receiver, so the communication can gap there.
Swetcha: Could you share a real-life example where you have faced such a thing?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, when I was,
kaushik ranjan: doing my bachelor's at Central University of Jaharkhand in mass communication. So, there, the diversity was across from all the states, from… people were from South Indian, people were from Northeast states.
kaushik ranjan: So, their communication can take a gap. Whatever is meant in our culture can be diff… can be different in their culture also. So, I had experience, when I was talking with them, there's some communication gap.
kaushik ranjan: Was there?
Swetcha: And how did you deal with it? How did you fix that communication gap?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, I, over the time when I understood about that, what it means in different languages, what it means in different cultures, so over the time, I understood, and I realized about it.
Swetcha: What do you do when instructions are unclear?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, at first, I will, try to understand the instructions.
kaushik ranjan: then only… I can work with it.
kaushik ranjan: Without infrastructure, it will be very, not possible to deal with the world.
Swetcha: How do you stay consistent over a long period?
Swetcha: I'm audible to you?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, stop.
Sushma: your order, Baron?
kaushik ranjan: I'm a web… Ma'am, I can stay consistent.
kaushik ranjan: Actually, I don't have answers for this question.
Sushma: No, for branding, we have to maintain the consistency, right? So, how will you do that?
Sushma: Consistency, promoting about the consistency of visibility and gradability, how to maintain that?
kaushik ranjan: Well… Actually, while working, we should be consistent, or the work culture can get disturbed.
Swetcha: So, if one audience group engages and another doesn't, how would you understand the difference?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, can you repeat again?
Swetcha: If one audience group engages to the content you're trying to promote and another doesn't, how would you understand the difference?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, ma'am, can I, ma'am, I have to explain about the gap between it, or something else?
Swetcha: Yes, you just need to tell me how would you engage different audience groups?
kaushik ranjan: actually, for… to engage different audience group, at first, we should understand their needs, what they need, and the… our goals. We have to align our goals and their need accordingly, so that it can make them engaging with our
kaushik ranjan: Content or something we are promoting.
kaushik ranjan: We have to align our ideas with their goals.
Swetcha: And if a campaign is not performing well, how would you analyze it?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, if a campaign is not performing well, we will try to understand where
kaushik ranjan: where the gap is occurring. A campaign can be due to some technical reasons, or if there is something problematic in understanding, we are using something which is not understandable by the audience.
kaushik ranjan: So, we can, do some correction with that, so that our potential audience can understand it.
Swetcha: Give me an example of organizing something into process.
kaushik ranjan: Organizing something to process.
Swetcha: Into a process, like something you have done before.
Swetcha: From a past life example.
Swetcha: From experience, you've learned something like that.
kaushik ranjan: Mom, actually, I didn't understand this question.
Swetcha: It just means,
Swetcha: Tell me about a time in your life where you helped in organizing a procedure.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, previously, I had worked with Jaharcan Tourism.
kaushik ranjan: Where we had to shoot some, tourism, we had to promote Jharkhand in terms of tourism. So, we had to, at the very basic stage, we were given trainings, and we had to shoot the raw footages of different locations.
kaushik ranjan: So, we have to do raw cuts and all, then we have to organize all the reels, all the raw footages, then we have to allow, add transition and all, and music.
kaushik ranjan: And then, logos were added, and then it was promoted to their official sites.
Swetcha: And if a lead drops after the first interaction, what will you do?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am?
Swetcha: lead drops after the first interaction, you had a first interaction with a lead, and then they are not responding back or communicating properly. What will you do in a situation like this?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, it can happen, all there.
kaushik ranjan: We… we have failed to understand them, their needs, so we will work with it and try to reorganize our content, our, our conversation again, so that we can gain,
Swetcha: And I'm done with my questions.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: So… Give us 2-3 minutes. Transha?
Sushma: Alright, let's go to that breakout room.
Swetcha: 14.
Swetcha: Hi, Claire.
Swetcha: We have a few more questions for… to check your organization fitment.
Swetcha: And then we'll be good to go.
Swetcha: Alright, so… Tell me about a time where you disagreed with a team member.
kaushik ranjan: Tell me about time when it's…
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, I had previously worked with,
kaushik ranjan: I had previously worked in the social media, like,
kaushik ranjan: Dharkan Tourism and in the PR field, where some of your ideas are,
kaushik ranjan: Some of your ideas are not good, or the teammates' ideas, so they're… when…
kaushik ranjan: I, I actually was working on the transition of,
kaushik ranjan: a video. So, actually, I was, applying my transitions, and they were, like, this is not good. So, at that time, we had to apply… I had to apply all the different transitions, and actually, I found that
kaushik ranjan: the ideas I was getting from the team was good, so at the end.
Swetcha: So you went with their ideas?
Swetcha: Alright. What does respect in a workplace mean to you?
kaushik ranjan: what those?
Swetcha: Respect in a world place mean to you?
kaushik ranjan: Actually, I am… I have not been a part of a bigger workplace in the past.
kaushik ranjan: I have worked as an intern in some of the fields, so…
kaushik ranjan: I don't have much idea about it.
Swetcha: Have you ever worked with someone who's, like, different from you?
kaushik ranjan: No, I'm… Why will I work with someone who is different from me?
Swetcha: Because that is what the organization structure is, and we require, We promote diversity at A4G.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, I have been with the diverse people, their culture were different, so I have managed to work with them
kaushik ranjan: In the past, also, I studied from an institution where the members of the institution were from diverse background.
kaushik ranjan: from all over the India. So, it will be easy for me to work with different diverse fields. It will help me to gain some… some of their experience, I will gain from them, and they will also… if I had something, they will also get something from me.
Swetcha: How would you say you are with adapting with new ideas or changes?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, I would, I would love to, Learn something new.
kaushik ranjan: So, if I get to learn about the new ideas or something, so it will be an additive for me.
kaushik ranjan: So, I will… Try to gain some hand-on knowledge and skills from The part of the world.
Swetcha: And if you join Umisha, what would you like to improve?
kaushik ranjan: What would you like to?
Swetcha: improve? What would you contribute to our team?
kaushik ranjan: Actually, I, this… ma'am, actually, this point I will better understand when I will be working with you.
kaushik ranjan: So, if there are new concepts, given from your side.
kaushik ranjan: So, I would love to, learn that if I had lacking some knowledge and skills, I would, I would very,
kaushik ranjan: Eager to learn, learn those aspects.
Swetcha: And if you are overwhelmed with work, what do you do?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, actually, you are not much audible.
Swetcha: Oh, then I'm sorry, Luke. Can you hear me now?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am.
Swetcha: Okay. If you are overwhelmed with work, what do you do?
kaushik ranjan: like a world…
kaushik ranjan: Actually, I didn't understand this.
Swetcha: Suppose you are in a situation where you have a lot of work on you. What do you do in a situation like that, when you're not able to handle your work?
kaushik ranjan: I'd… at, in this kind of situation, I would, when I would have more work.
kaushik ranjan: So I will be working in, part by part of the…
kaushik ranjan: work, I will complete, the work in, part by part, parting those work into fewer, fewer things. So, I will be completing one part, then moving to other part, then moving to other parts. So, in this way, I will not get bored, and I will be more engaging in the work.
Swetcha: Yes, Sushma Yanda, I will connect with you in the breakout room just once.
Sushma: Yeah, yeah.
Sushma: I'll just hold on for 2 minutes, kaushik.
kaushik ranjan: Okay, ma'am.
Sushma: Hi, kaushik.
Sushma: So, are you, an immediate joiner?
kaushik ranjan: this thumb.
Sushma: Mmm, okay.
Sushma: So, when you're having the exams, like, do you have any semester exams, or any mid-exams, or any semester exams?
kaushik ranjan: Programs will be conducted in December mode.
Sushma: Alright, alright. Currently, you don't have much exams also in place, okay? Because most of people will be concerned of having the exams, so they're requesting the link, so that's the thing I just want to check.
kaushik ranjan: Exams timing, whenever I will have exams in my college, it will be over till 12 to 1.
Sushma: Okay, alright.
Sushma: Are you confident enough to commit for 6 months with that stipend structure?
kaushik ranjan: Yes, ma'am.
Sushma: Do you have any, you know,
Sushma: Any concerns, or do you want to negotiate?
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, it was mentioned, in the,
Sushma: is mentioned in the job description, which is that is fixed, but I just want to know what is in your mind.
kaushik ranjan: If it is possible, then… but I had, joined the interview for what is mentioned in the LinkedIn slide.
Sushma: What is mentioned is fixed statue, there is no negotiation, I just asked. I just want to know what you're thinking, that's it.
Sushma: Alright.
Sushma: Any questions from your end?
kaushik ranjan: Oh, man.
Sushma: Nope.
kaushik ranjan: That's sweet.
Sushma: Nothing? Okay. So, we will update you. If you got shortlisted, just drop your contact number, email address, and phone number in the chat box.
Sushma: If you got shortlisted, you will hear from us.
kaushik ranjan: this one.
Sushma: For the next step.
Sushma: Okay.
Sushma: Next step means, you'll be having last panel round, which will be taken by operational leader.
kaushik ranjan: So…
Sushma: Yes.
kaushik ranjan: Ma'am, I have to drop my phone number in this chat box.
Sushma: Yeah.
Sushma: Phone number and email address. Okay.
Sushma: Thank you.
Sushma: That's it for today's interview. Thanks for joining.
Sushma: Have a nice day.